Ed SheeranPerfectLyricist：Ed SheeranComposer：Ed SheeranI found a love for meDarling, just dive right in and follow my leadI found a girl, beautiful and sweetI never knew you were the someone waiting for me'Cause we were just kids when we fell in loveNot knowing what it wasI will not give you up this timeBut darling, just kiss me slow, your heart is all I ownAnd in your eyes you're holding mineBaby, I'm dancing in the dark with you between my armsBarefoot on the grass, listening to our favorite songWhen you said you looked a mess, I whispered underneath my breathBut you heard it, darling, you look perfect tonightI found a woman, stronger than anyone I knowShe shares my dreams, I hope that someday I'll share her homeI found a love, to carry more than just my secretsTo carry love, to carry children of our ownWe are still kids, but we're so in loveFighting against all oddsI know we'll be alright this timeDarling, just hold my handBe my girl, I'll be your manI see my future in your eyesBaby, I'm dancing in the dark, with you between my armsBarefoot on the grass, listening to our favorite songWhen I saw you in that dress, looking so beautifulI don't deserve this, darling, you look perfect tonightBaby, I'm dancing in the dark, with you between my armsBarefoot on the grass, listening to our favorite songI have faith in what I seeNow I know I have met an angel in personAnd she looks perfect, no I don't deserve thisYou look perfect tonight