Jessie JPrice Tagokay,coconut man,moonheads,and meyou readySeems like everybody's got a price,I wonder how they sleep at night.When the sale comes first,And the truth comes second.Just stop, for a minute andSmile!Why is everybody so serious?Acting so damn mysterious.You got shades on your eyes.And your heels so high.That you can't even have a good time.Everybody looks to their left,(uh!)Everybody looks to their right!Can you feel that?(yeah!)We're paying with love tonight.It's not about the money, money, money,We don't need your money, money, money.We just wanna make the world dance,Forget about the price tag.Ain't about the(uh) cha-chang cha-chang.Ain't about the(yeah!) ba-bling ba-bling,Wanna make the world dance,Forget about the price tag.(Listen, okay.)We need to take it back in time,When music made us all UNITE!And it wasn't low blows, and video hoes,Am I the only one getting tired?Why is everybody so obsessed?Money can't buy us happiness.Can we all slow down and enjoy right now?Guarantee we'll be feeling all right.Everybody look to their left,(to the left)Everybody look to their right!(to the right)Can you feel that,(yeah!)We're paying with love tonight.It's not about the money, money, money,We don't need your money, money, money.We just wanna make the world dance,Forget about the price tag.Ain't about the(uh!) cha-chang cha-chang.Ain't about the(yeah!) ba-bling ba-bling,Wanna make the world dance,Forget about the price tag.Yeah, yeah...We'll, keep the price tag,And take the cash back.Just give me six strings(six strings) and a half stack,And you canCan keep the cars,Leave me the garage.And all IYes all I need are keys and guitars.And guess what?In 30 seconds I'm leaving to Mars!Yeah, we leaving across these undefeatable odds,And it's like this man, you can't put a price on my life.We do this for the love so we fight and sacrifice every night,So we ain't gonna stumble and fall.Never waiting to see a sign of defeat uh, uh!So we gonna keep everyone moving their feet,So bring back the beat, and then everyone sing,It's not about the money, money, money,We don't need your money, money, money.We just wanna make the world dance,Forget about the price tag.Ain't about the(uh) cha-chang cha-chiang.Ain't about the(yeah!) ba-bling ba-bling,Wanna make the world dance,Forget about the price tag.It's not about the money, money, money,We don't need your money, money, money.We just wanna make the world dance!Forget about the price tag.Ain't about the(yeah!) cha-chang cha-chang.Ain't about the(woo!) ba-bling ba-bling,Wanna make the world dance,Forget about the price tag.(uh-uh-uh-uh)Yeah yeah,(uh)Oo-oooh.(uh)Forget about the price tag.(uh-uh)